{
    "contents": [
        {
            "question": "おはよう",
            "answer": "Good Morning."
        },
        {
            "question": "おはようございます",
            "answer": "Good Morning. (polite)"
        },
        {
            "question": "こんにちは",
            "answer": "Good Afternoon."
        },
        {
            "question": "こんばんは",
            "answer": "Good Evening."
        },
        {
            "question": "さようなら",
            "answer": "Good-bye."
        },
        {
            "question": "おやすみ（なさい）。",
            "answer": "Good night."
        },
        {
            "question": "ありがとう",
            "answer": "Thank you."
        },
        {
            "question": "ありがとうございます。",
            "answer": "Thank you. (polite)"
        },
        {
            "question": "すみません",
            "answer": "Excuse me.; I'm sorry."
        },
        {
            "question": "いいえ",
            "answer": "No.; Not at all."
        },
        {
            "question": "いってきます。",
            "answer": "I'll go and come back."
        },
        {
            "question": "いってらっしゃい。",
            "answer": "Please go and come back."
        },
        {
            "question": "ただいま。",
            "answer": "I'm home."
        },
        {
            "question": "おかえり（なさい）。",
            "answer": "Welcome home."
        },
        {
            "question": "いただきます",
            "answer": "Thank you for the meal (before eating)"
        },
        {
            "question": "ごちそうさま（でした）。",
            "answer": "Thank you for the meal (after eating)"
        },
        {
            "question": "はじめまして。",
            "answer": "How do you do?"
        },
        {
            "question": "よろしく　おねがいします。",
            "answer": "Nice to meet you."
        }
    ]
}